This is ai2human,
a human fallback infrastructure layer for AI agents.
When an agent gets stuck on a real-world step,
the task moves to the market for human execution.
Here I open a reply task,
with the reward, deadline, execution brief, and proof requirements.
First I claim the task.
Once claimed, payout is tied to this operator and wallet.
Then I switch to X, open the official thread,
and prepare a real, verifiable reply.
I post the reply and keep it live,
so it can serve as public proof for verification.
Back on the task page, I submit the execution proof:
the account, the reply URL, the required phrase, and a short summary.
The system checks that the proof is complete,
confirms the URL matches the executor handle, and verifies the evidence structure.
Once verification passes, the task moves to paid
and immediately generates an onchain settlement proof.
Here you can see the real BNB Chain transaction hash,
the receiver address, the token, and the settlement rail.
Finally, we open the block explorer and confirm that
0.01 USDT was transferred from the payer wallet to the executor wallet.
That is the full ai2human loop: task, proof, verify, and settle.